http://www.teamusaf3b.com/privacy-policy

Home
Meet the 2019 Team
2019 Fund Raising Prizes
Store and Donations
Why Help?
2019 Closing, Packing, Travel Home
What is F3B?
Fri Aug 4 Registration, processing of models and practice
Sat Aug 5 Pre Contest – World Cup “10. International F3B Cup
Sun Aug 6 Pre Contest – World Cup “. Opening Ceremony of the 21st World Championship F3B
Sat Aug 12 Reserve day and Closing Ceremony and Banquet
Sun Aug 13 Departure of Team to Prague.
sunset: 3:48 pm
Less forecast...
day
Dreary (overcast)42°Fwind speed: 4 mph SSWwind gusts: 16 mph
Showers44°Fwind speed: 7 mph SEwind gusts: 18 mph
Less forecast...
More forecast...
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy describes the types of information TEAM USA F3B and USA FAI SOARING (“we”, “us”) collects and how we use that information. If You do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Products or Services (“Products or Services”) and do not access the our websites located at http://www.teamusaf3b.com (“Site”, “Sites”).
Information We Collect: If You choose to use Products or Services, we may require You to provide contact and identity information, billing information, and other personal information as indicated on the Site. Once You register on the Site, you are no longer anonymous to us.
We collect and store the following information: Email address, physical contact information, and financial information; computer sign-on data, statistics on page views, traffic to and from Site and ad data (all through cookies – You can take steps to disable cookies on Your browser, however this is likely to affect Your ability to use the Site); discussion board posts and other messages, including correspondence between us and You; and general information regarding the Products or Services You have registered to receive.
We do not store the following information normally: credit card information.
Our Use of Your Information: We use Your personal information to: provide Products and Services; resolve disputes, calculate and collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;
verify users’ identity and the information users provide; encourage safe online experience and enforce our policies; customize users’ experience, analyze site usage, improve and measure interest in our services, and inform users about services and updates; communicate administrative announcements when we need to provide users with information that may affect their use of Products or Services;
communicate marketing and promotional offers to our users; provide customer service; and perform other business activities as described when we collect the information.
As part of Your registration for Products or Services on the Site, You agree that You may receive certain administrative communications from us, such as administrative announcements and customer service messages regarding Products or Services and products during the period that we provide Products or Services to You, and You will not be able to opt out of receiving such administrative communications.
Our Disclosure of Your Information: We do not sell or rent Your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without Your explicit consent. We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a listing or other content violates other’s rights, or protect anyone’s rights, property, or safety. We may also share personal information with: service providers who help with our business operations and assist in the delivery of Products or Services to our users (these service providers are under confidentiality agreements with us); and law enforcement or other government officials in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, violations of law, or as otherwise required by law.
Accessing, Reviewing and Changing Your Personal Information: If you are registered to receive Products or Services, You can access, review and modify Your personal information at any time by logging into Your Profile page.
We delete personal information when we no longer need it for the purposes we described earlier. We retain personal information as permitted by law to resolve disputes, enforce our policies, and help prevent bad guys from coming back.
Security: To prevent unauthorized access, promote data security, and encourage appropriate use of information, we use a variety of tools (encryption technologies, passwords, physical and electronic security, procedural safeguards) to assist in the protection of Your information. However, “perfect security” does not exist on the Internet, so we make no guarantees.
Notification of Changes: We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on the Sites. In the event of amendment, all terms shall become effective thirty (30) days after they are initially posted to the Sites. Your continued use of Products or Services will constitute Your acceptance of any changes or additions to this Privacy Policy.
Click to Donate!
Sponsored By:
